<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Happy Baby</string>
    <string name="drawer_title" translatable="false">@string/app_name</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!--App Intro Text-->
    <string name="onboarding_intro_title">Welcome to Happy Baby</string>
    <string name="onboarding_intro_title_2">How it works</string>
    <string name="onboarding_intro_description">Happy Baby will help you feeding your child, such that it can grow big and strong.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_intro_description_2">Choose the foods you will feed your child today, and get advice on what you can do to improve his or her diet.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_add_photo_of_your_child_title">Add a picture</string>
    <string name="onboarding_add_photo_of_your_child_message">Tap on the camera icon to add a picture of your child</string>
    <string name="onboarding_select_age_of_your_child_title">How old is your child?</string>
    <string name="onboarding_select_age_of_your_child_message">This will help us give customized advice for your childs age</string>

    <!--Button Text-->
    <string name="button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="button_share_this_tip">Share this Tip</string>

    <!--Activities Titles-->
    <string name="title_activity_food_group_selection">Select Food Group</string>
    <string name="title_activity_food_selection">Select Food</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recipes">Porridge Recipes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_feedback">About your meal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sharing_this_tip">Share this Tip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sharing" translatable="false">SharingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_intro" translatable="false">IntroActivity</string>

    <!--Other Text-->
    <string name="message_start">Tap on start to select the foods you will feed your baby today</string>
    <string name="message_food_selection">What foods will I eat today?</string>

    <!--Navigation Drawer Items-->
    <string name="side_menu_item_porridge_recipes">Porridge Recipes</string>
    <string name="side_menu_item_FAQ">FAQ</string>
    <string name="side_menu_item_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="side_menu_item_about">About</string>

    <string name="options_menu_search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="options_menu_restart_title">Restart</string>
    <string name="options_menu_clear_list">Clear List</string>
    <string name="options_menu_restart_intro">Restart Intro</string>

    <!--Settings Menu-->
    <string name="settings_select_language">Select Language</string>
    <string name="settings_english">English</string>
    <string name="settings_khmer">ភាសាខ្មែរ</string>
    <string name="settings_age_of_your_child">Age of your child</string>
    <string name="settings_children_young_category">6\u20138 months</string>
    <string name="settings_children_middle_category">9\u201311 months</string>
    <string name="settings_children_old_category">12\u201324 months</string>
    <string name="settings_change_photo_your_child">Photo of your child</string>
    <string name="settings_alert_change_photo">Change photo</string>
    <string name="settings_alert_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="settings_alert_select_new_photo">Select new photo</string>
    <string name="settings_alert_delete_photo">Delete photo</string>
    <string name="settings_alert_take_new_photo">Take new photo</string>

    <!--Food Groups-->
    <string name="food_group_fruits">Fruits</string>
    <string name="food_group_legumes">Lentils, Pulses and Nuts</string>
    <string name="food_group_meat">Meat, Fish and Eggs</string>
    <string name="food_group_herbs">Herbs and Spices</string>
    <string name="food_group_vegetables">Vege\u00adtables</string>
    <string name="food_group_drinks">Drinks</string>
    <string name="food_group_carbohydrates">Staple Foods</string>
    <string name="food_group_last_used">Last Used</string>

    <!--Error Messages-->
    <string name="error_camera_permission">Camera Permission Error</string>
    <string name="error_write_ext_permission">External memory access Permission Error</string>

    <string name="about_open_source_licenses" translatable="false">Open-Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="about_credits" translatable="false">Credits</string>
    <string name="about_alert_close" translatable="false">Close</string>

    <!--String Arrays for selecting photo Alert Dialog-->
    <string-array name="select_photo_items_array">
        <item>@string/settings_alert_take_new_photo</item>
        <item>@string/settings_alert_select_new_photo</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="select_photo_items_array_with_delete">
        <item>@string/settings_alert_take_new_photo</item>
        <item>@string/settings_alert_select_new_photo</item>
        <item>@string/settings_alert_delete_photo</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--String Array for Open-Source Licenses-->
    <string-array name="about_items_array">
        <item>@string/about_open_source_licenses</item>
        <item>@string/about_credits</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Feedback overall Balanced/Unbalanced-->
    <string name="feedback_no_food_selected_title">No Food selected</string>
    <string name="feedback_no_food_selected_message">You did not select any foods</string>
    <string name="feedback_well_balanced_title">The meal is well balanced</string>
    <string name="feedback_well_balanced_message">You are doing great! Try to vary the meal every day and encourage your child to taste new foods.</string>
    <string name="feedback_not_well_balanced_title">The meal is not well balanced</string>
    <string name="feedback_not_well_balanced_message">Try to vary the meal every day and encourage your child to taste new foods.</string>

    <!--Feedback individual Food selection-->
    <string name="feedback_food_lack_of_fruit_vegetable_title">And what about fruits and vegetables?</string>
    <string name="feedback_food_lack_of_fruit_vegetable_message">Your baby needs fruits and vegetable everyday to stay healthy. Vegetables also help baby digestion! Encourage him/her to taste new fruits and vegetable according to the season!</string>
    <string name="feedback_food_lack_of_iron_title">The meal is not well balanced!</string>
    <string name="feedback_food_lack_of_iron_message">Your child needs a balanced diet to develop well and to be healthy. Try to add one of those foods in his/her meal (fish, meat, beans, crab, chicken, egg, or peas). It will help your baby to grow strong!</string>
    <string name="feedback_vitamin_A_present_title">Healthy choice!</string>
    <string name="feedback_vitamin_A_present_message">Eating food with high doses of vitamin A helps to give your babys better eyesight and lovely skin. When babies lack vitamin A this can lead to serious infections such as blindness.</string>
    <string name="feedback_not_suitable_present_title">Be careful!</string>
    <string name="feedback_not_suitable_present_message">Some foods are not suitable for your baby because they contain too many sugars, too much salt or chemicals. Try to replace with a healthier choice.</string>

    <!--Feedback General Take Away-->
    <string name="feedback_general_young_title">Baby is growing!</string>
    <string name="feedback_general_young">At 6 months, feeding only breast milk is not enough anymore. Your child needs to start eating other foods. Encourage him/her to try new foods and new textures little by little.</string>
    <string name="feedback_general_middle_title">Baby is discovering the world!</string>
    <string name="feedback_general_middle">Between 9 and 11 months, your child experiences a transition to grown up food. He/she wants to touch it. Make sure his/her hands are washed before eating.</string>
    <string name="feedback_general_old_title">Ready to walk!</string>
    <string name="feedback_general_old">At 1 year, your child is starting to walk. He/she needs more energy! He/she can eat the family meals but will need additional snacks every day. He/she wants to do what grown ups do and discover the world!</string>

    <!--Frequently Asked Questions-->
    <string name="FAQ_content">
        At what time, should I begin to feed my child with other foods, in addition to breastmilk?\n\n
        • At 6 months, the child need to begin to eat other foods to grow well, in addition to breastmilk.\n\n
        What is complementary feeding? \n\n
        • It is the period of transition from exclusive breastfeeding to family foods and it covers the period from 6-23 months of age\n\n
        How can I help my 6 months’ baby to get used to new foods?\n\n
        • To help your baby discover new tastes and get used to a new food, introduce 1 new food at a time, in small quantity.  Encourage him/her to eat! Show him/her that you also taste the food and like it.\n\n
        What can I do to have enough breastmilk for my child?\n\n
        • Eat and drink a bit more. Breastfeed when the child show signs of hunger, and continue to breastfeed during the night.\n\n
        At 6 month, how much food should I give to my baby in addition to breastmilk?\n\n
        • At 6 months, if the child is breastfed, 2-3 spoons of bobor will be enough. Increase little by little the quantity and continue to breastfeed.\n\n
        What kind of food can I give to my 6 months’ baby?\n\n
        • At 6 months, your baby can be given rice, sweet potatoes, fish, eggs, vegetables, but remember to give 1 new food at a time at the beginning! Food must be soft but thick in consistency.\n\n
        What can I give to my child 7-8 months old?\n\n
        • At 7-8 months, your baby can eat more variety of food! Try to give him rice, sweet potato or taro, as a staple, with a bit of Fish, meat, liver, egg or beans (peanut, mungbean) and some vegetables such as morning glory, ivy gourd leaves, star gooseberry leaves (ngub), amaranth leaves, pumpkin squash or leaves, or moringa leaves (marom) etc. Add a little oil to increase the energy content and make the food tasty.\n\n
        How much food should I give to my child at 7-8 months?\n\n
        • Your baby should eat to 3 times per day in addition to breastmilk. At 6-7, a baby can eat up to half a bowl (Chan Chang Koeh) at each meal. The baby appetite can vary a lot from one to another, encourage him/her to eat but don/t force him/her.  The baby will be able to know when he/she is satisfied.\n\n
        What can I do if my child refuse to eat?\n\n
        • Your baby is discovering new things every day, he/she need time to get used to new tastes, and new textures. Don’t force him/her.  Eating should be a nice time between child and parents. Encourage you baby gently and propose something else if the child refuse a specific kind of food. Show him/her you are eating the same food. Children generally eat more when they eat together with their parents.\n\n
        What can I cook for a child 7-8months?\n\n
        • Look at the recipe section to get ideas (link to recipe)\n\n
        What can I give to drink to a child 6-23 months?\n\n
        • Your child can continue to take breastmilk until he/she is 23 moths. At 6 months, you can begin to give a bit of natural juice and water. The water should be treated (boiled, bottle water or chlorinated) to make sure your baby can take it without getting sick. If you give him/her juice, don’t add any sugar or honey, there is enough natural sugar in fruits. Don’t give any soda/soft drinks, they contain too much sugar and chemicals.\n\n
        Why is it not recommended to give soft drink to babies?\n\n
        • Soft drinks contain too much sugar and chemicals.  It is not healthy for babies: the sugar is a strong excitant and will alter his/her mood and sleep.\n\n
        Why is it not recommended for a baby to drink tea?\n\n
        • Tea is an excitant. It will disturb the sleep of your baby. Drinking tea make it difficult for your child to get the good nutrients from food. He/she will not be able to get the iron he/she need to grow strong and healthy. This is why it is not recommended to give tea to babies.\n\n
        </string>
</resources>
